☆独家制作☆
喜马拉雅主播 & 微信公众号:
美国青少年英语
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
[loud thrumming]
[both] the gate.
‎门
I don't understand.
You've seen this before?
‎我不明白 你之前见过这个？
- Not exactly.
- Then what, exactly?
‎-不完全是
‎-那具体是什么？
- All you need to know is it's bad.
- [Steve] it's really bad.
‎-你只需要知道这很糟糕就行了
‎-非常糟糕
Like, end-of-the-human-race-as-we-know-it
kind of bad.
‎像我们已知的人类物种灭绝那么糟糕
And you know about this how?
‎你们怎么会知道的？
Um, steve? Where's your russian friend?
‎史蒂夫 你的俄国朋友呢？
[alarm blaring]
shit.
‎妈的
[yelling in russian]
halt! Halt!
‎停下！
Shit.
‎妈的
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- [Dustin] shit.
‎快跑！
[steve] move! Let's move!
[office chair squeaks]
[steve] go! Shit! Shit, shit, shit!
‎-妈的！
‎-快跑！
[steve] go, go, go!
[yelling in russian]
[shrieks]
[dustin] holy shit!
Holy shit! Holy shit!
‎我的天哪！
Shit! Holy shit! Holy shit!
[gasps for air] holy shit!
- Guards! Go!
- This way!
‎-有守卫！快跑！
‎-这边
- [Grunting]
- [guards yelling in russian]
- [steve] oh, shit! Oh, shit!
- [Erica] whoa!
‎-哦 妈的！
‎-快跑！
[steve grunts]
- come on! Go, go, go, go, go!
- [Robin] come on!
‎-赶紧的 快跑啊！
‎-快跑！
- Shit!
- [Robin] this way!
‎-妈的！
‎-这边走！
- [Robin] come on, quick!
- [Steve] hold the door!
‎-快来！
‎-开着门！
[yelling in russian]
robin!
‎走了 快点！
Shit!
‎妈的！
[yelling in russian]
- [steve] help me, come on!
- [Erica] here! Come on, let's go!
‎-帮帮我！
‎-这边 快点啊 我们走！
[yelling in russian]
- come on!
- Go! Just get out of here!
‎-快来啊！
‎-快跑！快走！
Go, come on, now!
‎快跑！现在就走！
No! Just go get some help, okay?
‎不！快去找人帮忙吧 好吗？
[steve] what are you doing?!
‎你在干什么？
- [Both] go!
- [Guards yelling]
‎-快走！
‎-我不会忘了你们的
I won't forget you!
[both] go!
‎快走！
[robin yelps, grunts]
[yelling in russian]
[guns cocking]
[flourescent lights buzzing]
[low frequency rumbling]
[fluttering sound]
he's here.
‎他在这里
[will shivers]
[eleven breathes deeply]
[shrieking]
- shit.
- Nancy!
‎-妈的
‎-南茜！
[jonathan] run!
‎快跑！
[nancy] damn!
hey!
‎嘿！
[nancy grunts]
[jonathan] come on!
‎快跑啊！
- [Roars]
- [nancy whimpers]
hey!
‎嘿
hey, hey, hey! Two at a time!
‎一次只能两个人！
[creature shrieking]
[panting]
[snarling]
[creature snarls, growls]
[nancy whimpers]
[creature snarls]
[shrieking]
[pounding on door]
[panting]
[clanging]
[jonathan grunts]
[snarling]
[squelching sound]
oh, my god.
‎天哪
[intense synth music playing]
jonathan...
‎乔纳森
No! Nancy!
‎不 南茜！
Jonathan!
‎乔纳森！
[grunts]
no, no! Nancy!
‎不 南茜！
[beeping]
stairs.
‎楼梯
Goddamn it!
‎该死！
[bubbling and squelching]
[snarling]
[roaring]
[panting]
[creature squelches]
[creature snarling]
[snarling continues]
[creature growling]
[roaring]
[shrieking]
- jesus!
- What the f...
‎-天哪！
‎-什么鬼？
[roaring]
- [eleven yells]
- [creature wails]
- [creature groans]
- [yells]
- [creature shrieks]
[yells]
- [snarls]
- [eleven yells]
- go.
- Nancy!
‎-快走
‎-南茜 快走！
Are you okay? Are you okay?
‎你没事吧？
[all panting]
[lights buzzing]
[squelching]
[eerie synth music playing]
[bubbling and squelching]
[rhythmic grunting]
[squelching sound]
[creature grunts]
it's time.
‎是时候了
[creature shrieks]
‎NETFLIX 原创剧集
[theme music playing]
‎第六集：合众为一
["stand up and meet
your brother" playing]
‎（克莱恩市长特别呈现 嘉年华）
[indistinct chatter]
♪ stand up and meet
your brother, honey ♪
♪ one color or another ♪
♪ but he's still ♪
♪ he's still your brother ♪
♪ reach out and take his hand ♪
♪ I want y'all to ♪
- [grumbles]
- ♪ help him understand... ♪
hey! Excuse me.
‎嘿 打扰一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
‎打扰一下
What... What are you doing?
What's... What's this doing here?
‎你在干什么？这玩意在这儿干什么？
- What?
- Your stand.
‎-什么?
‎-你的小摊
It's right in the main thoroughfare.
‎正挡在大道上了
Where do you want it, sir?
‎你要我搬到哪里 先生？
[scoffs]
over there with the rest
of the goddamn food stalls.
‎去那边 和其他该死的食品摊放一起
It isn't rocket science.
‎又不是难事
Sheesh, do I have to
do everything myself?
‎难以置信 一切都要我亲自做吗？
[ominous synth music playing]
[clears throat]
[larry] my friends in state pd,
‎我的州警察局的朋友
highway patrol, they're
all on the lookout.
‎高速公路巡警都在监视着
I got eyes everywhere.
‎到处都有眼线
The second he pops up...
‎只要他一出现
I get a call.
‎我就会接到电话
A call?
‎电话？
Yes. A call. [chuckles]
‎是的 电话
I mean, what more do
you people want me to do?
‎你们还想让我做什么？
We want you to find him.
‎我们想要你找到他
[sucks lips]
let me explain something to you.
‎让我和你解释一件事
This man is a moron, okay?
‎这个人是个蠢瓜 好吗？
He's driving around in a yellow
convertible, for christ's sakes.
‎老天
‎他居然开着黄色的敞篷车到处跑
He sticks out like a sore thumb.
‎很惹人注目
I will find him.
‎我会找到他的
And, when I do,
‎等我找到了
‎我能不能建议你这次多带点后援去？
may I suggest you bring some
backup with you this time?
- Backup.
- Some comrades.
‎-后援
‎-带一些同志去
Since last time, he
got the better of you.
‎因为上次他占了上风
[larry grunts]
- [door whines shut]
- [carnival music playing]
- [larry groans]
- [hissing noise]
[ride powers up]
please...
‎拜托
I... I didn't mean that.
‎我不是那个意思
You... You don't need backup.
‎你不需要后援
This man is your fault,
‎这个人是你的失误导致的 你的问题
your problem.
You're lucky you still breathe.
‎你还活着就已经很幸运了
[choking] very lucky.
‎非常幸运
Please.
‎拜托
I'm sorry.
‎对不起
I... I have a bad temper.
‎我脾气不好
I'm going to therapy.
‎我会去接受心理咨询的
You have one day to
find this man for me.
‎你有一天的时间给我找到这个人
Nod if you understand.
‎明白的话就点个头
[choking]
[playful orchestral music playing]
[hopper] two whoppers,
‎两个皇堡
extra ketchup, large fry,
‎额外的番茄酱 大薯条
pack of marlboro reds,
‎一包红色万宝路
and one extra-large...
‎还有一杯加大的思乐冰
Slurpee.
Burger king is nowhere near
the 7-eleven, by the way.
‎顺便说 汉堡王离711便利店远着呢
Never said it was.
‎我可没说离得近
Let's try this again. Joyce.
‎我们再试一次吧 乔伊斯
Alexei,
‎阿列克谢 那些发电机
the generators,
what are they powering?
‎是给什么发电的？
And tell him that we know
it is not the starcourt mall,
‎告诉他我们知道不是星庭商场了
so he can stop selling us that crap.
‎所以他不需要再试图哄骗我们了
[in russian] those generators
you were working on,
‎你工作的那些发电机
‎是给什么东西发电的？
what are you powering?
We know it's not the mall.
‎我们知道不是商场了
[in russian] this tastes
like shit strawberry.
‎这个味道像狗屎草莓
- What'd he say?
- He says,
‎-他说什么？
‎-他说
"it's strawberry."
‎草莓味的
I'm sorry?
‎对不起？
His... Slurpee.
‎他的思乐冰
[murray] he says it's strawberry.
‎他说是草莓味的
So what?
‎所以呢？
Hop, he did ask for cherry. I mean...
‎霍珀 他的确问你要的是樱桃味的
Well, they didn't have cherry.
‎他们没有卖樱桃味的
They didn't have it.
‎没有的卖
And it doesn't matter,
‎而且也不重要
because it all tastes the same, okay?
‎因为尝起来都一样 好吗？
It is sugar on ice. You tell him that.
‎就是糖加冰 你这么告诉他
Tell him what?
‎告诉他什么？
You tell him that it all
tastes the goddamn same!
‎告诉他尝起来都他妈是一样的！
[murray, in russian] it's all the same.
‎都是一样的
Sugar on ice. No difference.
‎糖加上冰 没什么区别
[in russian] tell that stupid man
it is not the same in the slightest,
‎告诉那个愚蠢的男人一点都不一样
and I would like the cherry I requested.
‎我想要我要求的樱桃味的
[in english] he respectfully disagrees.
‎他尊重地表示不同意
[murray] it's not the same at all,
‎完全不同
and he would like...
‎他想要樱桃味的
- Cherry.
- [Chuckles]
oh, yeah? You tell
him... He can forget it.
‎是吗？你告诉他...别想了
[in russian] he says
forget it. No cherry.
‎他说别想了 没有樱桃味的
[in russian] no cherry, no deal.
‎没有樱桃味的 就没的谈
[laughs]
[in english] he says,
‎他说："没有樱桃味的 就没的谈"
"no cherry...
No deal."
[smacks lips]
[murray] yeah.
‎没错
hm.
[inhales sharply]
mm.
- [hopper yells]
- [murray] oh, shit!
- [Yelling]
- [joyce] no, hop...
‎-哦 该死的 喂！
‎-不要啊！
- [Grunting]
- wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
- I'm not gonna hurt him!
- [Joyce] what are you doing?
‎-等一下
‎-我不会伤害他的
- [Hopper growls]
- come on! Come on!
‎你在干什么？
‎拜托！
I'm just giving him an opportunity
‎我只是给他一个机会
to get his own damn...
‎自己去搞他想要的
Cherry slurpee!
‎樱桃味思乐冰
- [Hopper grunts]
- [alexei whimpers]
[whimpers]
jim, that man is an enemy of the state.
‎吉姆 那个人是国家公敌
Yeah, who's been jerking
us around for a full day!
‎他一整天都把我们耍得团团转
I get him his cherry slurpee, then what?
‎我给他买樱桃味的思乐冰 之后呢？
He wants a helicopter to charter
him to his own private island.
‎他想要包一架直升机
‎把他送去他的私人岛屿
I have dealt with assholes like this
‎我一辈子都在和这样的混蛋打交道
my entire life.
[hopper] yesterday in the
woods, he could've escaped,
‎昨天在树林里 他本来可以逃跑的
‎但他没有逃跑
- but he didn't.
- [Chuckles]
he stuck with us.
‎还是和我们待在了一起
Why do you think that is?
‎你觉得这是为什么？
It's because...
‎因为他害怕
He's scared.
[hopper] he's scared.
‎他害怕
Not of us,
‎不是害怕我们
of them.
‎害怕他们
He's scared of that
seven-foot-tall russian freak
‎他害怕那个两米高的俄国怪胎
who could've killed him
just as easily as us.
‎他杀他就像杀我们一样容易
Smirnoff knows
‎斯米诺伏特加知道
that if he runs back to his
comrades without a scratch on him,
‎如果他毫发无损地逃回同胞身边
they're gonna think
that he spilled his guts.
‎他们会以为他出卖了机密
So, whether he likes it or not, we...
‎所以不管他喜不喜欢 我们...
Are the best chance he's got.
‎就是他最好的机会了
Ooh! [grunts in pain]
I give him 30 seconds before
he comes knocking on that door,
‎最多三十秒 他就会来敲门了
right back into our arms,
‎重新回到我们的怀抱
with a new sense of humility.
‎怀着新的谦卑感
- ["neutron dance" plays]
- ♪ I don't wanna take it anymore ♪
[laughs giddily]
- jim...
- Uh...
‎吉姆 我觉得他开动了车
I, uh, believe he has started the car.
Hopper.
‎霍珀
You know, testing us.
He's just calling my bluff.
‎他在考验我们 想戳穿我的计谋
♪ 'cause I work so hard
to make it every day ♪
♪ woo-ooh ♪
I believe he is now driving away.
‎我觉得他现在正在把车给开走
[grumbles]
[scoffs]
[joyce grumbles] jim. Jim, move.
‎-吉姆 让开
‎-乔伊斯...
- Joyce, joyce...
- Move, move, move!
♪ yeah ♪
♪ ooh-ooh, huh ♪
♪ and it's hard to say ♪
♪ just how some things never change ♪
♪ and it's hard to find ♪
♪ any strength to draw the line ♪
♪ ooh, I'm just burning
doin' the neutron dance ♪
♪ I'm just burning
[engine switches off]
♪ I know there's a pot of gold for me ♪
♪ all I've got to do
is just believe... ♪
[muttering in russian]
♪ doin' the neutron dance ♪
♪ and I'm just burning... ♪
i'm sorry, what did he say?
‎抱歉 他说了什么？
He says he likes strawberry, too.
‎他说草莓味的他也喜欢
- ♪ I'm just burning ♪
- ♪ in my feet ♪
♪ doin' the neutron dance, woo-hoo ♪
[dustin] so, when we
set fire to the hub,
‎所以我们点燃了枢纽
we drew the demodogs away
so el could close the gate.
‎把魔狗支开 让艾尔关上门
But now, for some insane reason,
‎但现在 出于一些疯狂的原因
the russians appear to
be trying to reopen it,
‎俄国人似乎想要重新打开这个门
which just destroys everything
we risked our lives for.
‎这就摧毁了
‎我们冒着生命危险所做的一切努力
By "we", you're including lucas?
‎你说"我们"的时候包括卢卡斯在内？
Yes, of course.
‎当然了
So, all that shit you
told me, lucas was there?
‎所以你刚和我说的那么多事情
‎卢卡斯全都在场？
- Yeah.
- My brother, lucas charles sinclair?
‎-是啊
‎-我哥哥 卢卡斯查尔斯辛克莱尔？
yes!
‎是的
I don't believe you.
‎我不信
Wait, so you believe
everything about el and the gate
‎慢着
‎所以你相信所有那些关于艾尔、门
and the demodogs and the mind flayer,
‎魔狗和夺心魔的事情
but you question your
brother's involvement?
‎却质疑你哥哥是否参与了其中？
That's correct.
‎没错
Makes total sense.
‎完全说得通
- Um, you need help with that?
- No.
‎-你需要帮忙吗？
‎-不用
- Well, I mean, it's taking a while, so...
- Yeah, no shit, sherlock.
‎-我想说的是 花了好久了 所以...
‎-是啊 废话 福尔摩斯
All right, so if we don't find
‎好的 如果我们无法找到
‎更有效的让这些风扇停转的办法
a more efficient method
to stop these fans,
we're never gonna find help,
‎我们永远也找不到人帮忙
‎你的冰淇淋小伙伴们就死定了
and your ice cream buddies are screwed.
Yeah, with that attitude,
they are. Jee-zus!
‎是啊 就你那态度
‎他们可不是死定了 老天
I'm just being realistic.
‎我只是务实考虑
I mean, we've made it about
point-three miles in nine hours.
‎我们九个小时走了480米
Then we had to walk three
hours down that tunnel,
‎我们花三个小时才走完那个隧道
so I'd estimate ten miles
back to the elevator,
‎所以我估计走回电梯还需要16公里
which should take us approximately
twelve-and-a-half days.
‎大约需要12天半的时间
Did you just do all
of that in your head?
‎你这些都是心算出来的？
I'm good with numbers.
‎我数学很好
Holy shit. You're a nerd.
‎我的妈呀 你是个书呆子
Come again?
‎再说一遍？
You... Are... A... Nerd.
‎你是个书呆子
Okay, you better take that back, nerd.
‎-喂 你最好收回这句话 书呆子
‎-可没办法把真相放回盒子里
Can't put the truth back in the box.
- But it's not the truth.
- Let's examine the facts, shall we?
‎-但这不是真相
‎-那让我们看一看事实吧 好吗？
Fact one: you're a
math whiz, apparently.
‎事实一 你居然是个数学奇才
That was a pretty
straightforward equation.
‎那不过是个非常直接的方程式而已
Fact number two: you're
a political junkie.
‎事实二 你对政治上瘾
Just because I don't agree
with communism as an ideology...
‎就因为
‎我不同意共产主义这个意识形态...
Fact number three: you
love my little pony.
‎事实三 你特别喜欢《小马宝莉》
And what does my little
pony have to do with this?
‎《小马宝莉》和这些有什么关系？
Ah, let's recall the ponies'
latest adventure, shall we?
‎让我们回忆一下小马宝莉
‎最近的一次历险吧？
The evil centaur team and tirek
‎邪恶的马人团队和提雷克
turns applejack into a
dragon at midnight castle,
‎在午夜城堡将苹果嘉儿变成了一条龙
and then megan and the other
ponies have to use moochick's magic
‎然后梅根和其他小马
‎不得不使用月亮地精的魔法
to defeat his rainbow of darkness,
‎打败黑暗彩虹
saving them from a
lifetime of enslavement.
‎让他们免于永生被奴役的命运
All the pink in the world can't
disguise the irrefutable fact
‎全世界所有粉色加在一起
‎也无法掩饰一个不争的事实
that centaurs and castles
and dragons and magic
‎马人、城堡、龙、魔法
‎这些都是书呆子标配
are all standard nerd tropes.
Ergo, my little pony is nerdy.
‎所以 《小马宝莉》是个书呆子动画
Ergo, you, erica,
‎所以 你 艾瑞卡 是个书呆子
are a nerd.
And how do you know so
much about my little pony?
‎那你为什么这么了解《小马宝莉》？
Because I'm...
‎因为我是...
A nerd.
‎一个书呆子
[electricity crackles]
[powering down noise]
let's go...
‎走吧 书呆子
Nerd.
You...
‎你...
[steve groans]
that one stung.
‎这一下好痛
[gasps for air]
who do you work for?
‎你到底为谁工作？
For the millionth time,
I work at scoops ahoy!
‎说了一百万次了 水手冰淇淋
Scoops ahoy.
‎水手冰淇淋
[groans]
[steve] what the hell?!
‎什么鬼？
Look at my outfit!
‎瞧瞧我穿的衣服啊！
You think I just wear this?!
‎你以为我平时就这么穿？
‎以为我是穿水手服的间谍？
Think I'm a spy in a sailor's uniform?
[groans]
[grunts]
how did you get in?
‎你是怎么进来的？
[gasps] I already told you.
‎我已经告诉过你了
I told you before. [gasps for air]
‎之前就告诉你了
my delivery didn't come,
‎有一批货没到
and my friends and i,
‎我朋友和我以为货被落在装货码头了
we thought that it was
left at the loading dock,
so we went in the room, and
then it turned into an elevator,
‎所以我们进了房间
‎结果房间变成了一个电梯
and then... And then
we dropped and then,
‎然后我们被甩了下来 然后
next thing we know, I open my eyes,
‎我一睁开眼睛
and we're in this...
‎就来到了这个美好的地方
Wonderful facility.
But I swear to god,
‎但是我向上帝发誓
nobody knows about us, nobody saw us.
‎没人知道我们是谁 没人见过我们
You could just let us go, all right?
‎你可以放我们走 好吗？
And I'm not gonna tell
anybody about this, okay?
‎我不会告诉任何人的 好吗？
Shit happens, life goes on.
‎糟糕的事时有发生 生活还要继续
And, uh... Ice... Ice cream.
‎还有...冰淇淋 对不对？
Ice cream, okay?
You guys know what ice cream
is. Everybody loves ice cream.
‎你们知道什么是冰淇淋吧
‎所有人都爱冰淇淋
I don't know if you
have russian ice cream
‎我不知道你们有没有俄国冰淇淋
or if that's considered gelato.
‎还是说你们的冰淇淋偏意式了
I don't know what's what, but
whatever you guys want, seriously.
‎不知道这些乱七八糟的
‎但你们想要吃什么都行 认真的
Uss butterscotch, I
mean, you gotta try it.
‎美国军舰奶油硬糖号 你必须要尝尝
It is out of this world, I'm telling ya!
‎无与伦比的美味 我告诉你
[soldiers laughing]
[laughs nervously]
‎我喜欢这家伙
I like this guy!
"uss... Butterscotch." [laughs]
‎美国军舰奶油硬糖号
[soldiers continue laughing]
[chuckles]
[laughter stops]
who do you work for?
‎你为谁工作？
Oh, come on. No, no! No, seriously...
‎拜托 别 认真的...
[soldier grunts]
[soldiers speaking russian]
[grunting]
get your hands off me!
‎放开我！嘿！停手！把你的...
[yelps, grunts]
hey...
‎嘿
Steve?
‎史蒂夫？
- [Door buzzer sounds]
- steve? Steve?
Steve?
What did you do to him? What did you do?
‎你们对他做了什么？
- [Officer grunts]
- [robin groans]
[whimpers]
[in russian] put them in the chairs.
‎把他们放到椅子上
[soldier speaks russian]
[robin] don't touch me!
‎别碰我 史蒂夫...
Steve... [grunts]
steve, wake up. Steve?
‎史蒂夫 醒醒啊 史蒂夫？
[robin grunts, yelps]
what did you do?!
‎你们对他做了什么？
[robin grunts]
don't touch him.
‎别碰他
[clicking tongue]
steve? Steve, can you hear me?
‎史蒂夫 能听见我说话吗？
[officer, in english] I think
your friend need a doctor.
‎我觉得你朋友需要看医生了
Good thing...
‎好消息
We have the very best.
‎我们有最好的医生
[officer laughs]
[soldiers laugh]
you are going to regret
that, little bitch.
‎你会后悔的 婊子
[speaks russian]
‎我们走
[door buzzer sounds]
bastards.
‎混账
Let us outta here!
‎放我们走
Bastards! Let us out! Let us out!
‎混账 放我们走！
[water splashing gently]
[ominous synth music playing]
[static hissing]
[mike] it can't be good for her
to be in there for this long.
‎她在里面待这么久
‎肯定对她身体不好吧
Mike, you need to relax.
‎迈克 你需要放松
What if she gets brain
damage or something?
‎如果她脑损伤怎么办？
Oh, shit. Is that, like, a real thing?
‎哦 妈的 真的有这种事吗？
No, it's not. He made it up.
‎不是的 是他瞎编的
‎迈克不知道自己在说什么
Mike doesn't know what
he's talking about.
- Oh, and you do?
- No, I...
‎-哦 所以你知道？
‎-不是 我...
Yes, from the hawkins post.
‎是的 《霍金斯邮报》的
I... I called a couple
days ago about the...
‎我几天前打电话问过...是的
- [Indistinct male voice on phone]
- yes, yes, um...
I was just...
‎我只是想跟进一下
‎还有什么其他东西消失吗？
Following up to see if
anything else had gone missing,
or if... Okay.
‎或者...好的
Um, sorry to bother...
‎抱歉打扰...
[dial tone sounding]
[max and mike argue
indistinctly in background]
- [nancy sighs] who's next?
- [Jonathan] there is no next.
‎-接下来是哪家？
‎-没有了
Unless you want to start
calling random people's homes.
‎除非你想开始随便给人家里打电话
- It doesn't make sense.
- What part of any of this makes sense?
‎-这说不通
‎-有哪一部分说得通吗？
There's a pattern, okay? A
consistency to their behavior.
‎有相应模式的 好吗？
‎他们的行为是有一致性的
They've been feeding on these
chemicals since this started,
‎从这件事一开始
‎他们就开始吃这些化学品
and... And, what, they
just stop, out of the blue?
‎然后呢 他们就这样突然停止了？
Maybe they have all
the chemicals they need.
‎也许他们需要的化学品都有了
Maybe they've all turned
into those... Things.
‎也许他们都已经变成了那些东西
But what about the source?
‎那源头呢？
I mean, did the mind flayer just
suddenly stop infecting people?
‎夺心魔突然就不再感染其他人了吗？
And even if the flayed are monsters
now, why can't el find them?
‎就算被夺心的人现在已经变成了怪物
‎艾尔为什么找不到他们？
Okay, can you guys
settle an argument for us?
‎你们能帮我们评个理吗？
Who do you think should
decide el's limits?
‎你觉得艾尔的限度应该由谁来决定？
Mike or eleven?
‎迈克还是十一？
The way that you frame
that is such bullshit.
‎你用这样的方式说也太胡扯了
It's not bullshit, mike.
This is your whole problem.
‎不是胡扯 迈克 这就是你的问题所在
And it's also precisely the
reason why she dumped your ass.
‎也是她为什么甩了你的原因
El dumped you?
‎艾尔甩了你？
Yeah, because she is
conspiring against me.
‎是的 因为她在密谋反叛我
‎她给她施加了太多坏影响
She's corrupting her.
No, enlightening her.
‎不 我是在开导她
[max] the fact is, she's not yours.
‎事实是 她不是你的人
She's her own person, fully
capable of making her own decisions.
‎她是独立的人
‎完全有能力做自己的决定
She's risking her life for no reason.
‎她无缘无故地拿自己的生命冒险
For no reason?
‎无缘无故？迈克
‎被夺心的人在外面做着鬼知道什么事
Mike, the flayed are out
there doing god knows what.
- Killing, flaying...
- Transforming into monsters.
‎-杀人 夺心...
‎-变成怪物
And el's not stupid.
‎艾尔也不蠢
[nancy] she knows her
abilities better than any of us.
‎她对自己的能力的了解
‎比我们多得多
- Exactly, thank you.
- And she is her own person.
‎-没错 谢谢你
‎-她也是独立的人
- Exactly.
- With her own free will.
‎-没错
‎-有自己的自由意志
[max] exactly.
‎没错
El has saved the world twice,
and mike still doesn't trust her.
‎艾尔已经两次拯救世界
‎迈克却仍然不信任她
You wanna talk about trust, really?
‎你真的想说信任？
‎是你让十一监视我们的
After you made eleven spy on us?
- Wait, what?
- Oh, she didn't tell you this?
‎-慢着 什么？
‎-哦 她没告诉你们吗？
- No.
- Your girlfriend used el's powers
‎-没有
‎-你女朋友利用艾尔的能力
- to spy on us.
- No, no, no, I did not make her.
‎-监视我们
‎-不 我没有利用她
It was her idea.
‎本来就是她的主意
And why are we even talking
about this, seriously?
‎认真说 我们为什么还在讨论这些？
Yeah, who cares?
‎是啊 谁在乎？
- I care.
- Yeah.
‎-我在乎
‎-好吧
I guess girlfriends don't lie, they spy.
‎-我猜女朋友不会撒谎 而是监视
‎-我们只是在闹着玩
We were just joking around.
Wouldn't it've been so funny
‎如果我当时刚好在拉屎什么的
‎会不会特别好玩？
if I was taking a massive
shit or something?
- You weren't.
- But what if I was?
‎-你没在拉屎
‎-万一我在拉屎呢？
- Then gross!
- Seriously, mike?
‎-那就恶心死了！
‎-真的吗 迈克？
I'm just trying to
demonstrate how careless
‎我只是想表达麦克斯
‎对十一的能力有多么马虎
max is with eleven's powers.
In fact, how careless all of you are.
‎事实上 你们所有人都是
You're treating her like
some kind of machine
‎你们把她当成某种机器看待
‎但她不是什么机器
when she's not a machine,
and I don't want her to
die looking for the flayed
‎我不希望她找被夺心者的时候牺牲
when they've obviously vanished
off the face of the earth.
‎这些人很明显已经从地球上消失了
So can we please just
come up with a new plan
‎所以能不能拜托想一个新计划
‎因为我爱她
because I love her and
I can't lose her again.
‎我不能再失去她一次了
[door opening]
what's going on?
‎出什么事了？
Nothing. Nothing.
‎没什么
Just a family discussion.
‎家庭讨论而已
oh.
I found him.
‎我找到他了
Found who?
‎找到谁了？
[murray] he calls it the key,
and this key emits a great energy.
‎他将其称之为钥匙
‎这个钥匙会发出巨大的能量
[alexei speaking russian]
[murray] it requires
much strength, power.
‎它需要很大的力量 电力
[alexei speaking russian]
[murray] those houses,
like the one you found,
‎你们找到的那种房子
they're located near, uh, transformers.
‎位于变压器附近
They're stealing from
your town's power grid.
‎他们在从你们的电网上偷窃
Why build this key here?
‎为什么要在这里建这个钥匙？
‎不能在自己的后院建吗？
Why are they not doing
this in their own backyard?
What are they trying to
do, blow us to smithereens?
‎他们想干什么？把我们都炸成碎片？
[speaking russian]
[chuckles lightly]
there were many of these,
uh, keys before in russia,
‎俄国以前有很多这种钥匙
but they turned out wrong.
‎但是最后发现是错的
[alexei speaking russian]
they had to come to where
the... Where the, uh...
‎他们必须要来到这个...
Where the what?
‎什么？
- I don't understand what he's saying.
- I thought you were fluent.
‎-我不明白他在说什么
‎-你不是说你很流利吗？
Oh, I'm sorry.
‎哦 抱歉
Are my free translation
services not good enough for you?
‎对我的免费翻译服务不满意？
Because you can just go
ahead and file your complaint
‎冲着我的屁眼投诉！
right up my ass!
What is smirnoff doing?
‎斯米诺伏特加这是在干什么？
- He's showing me.
- [Speaking russian]
‎他在向我展示
[murray] oh, okay.
‎好吧 他说这个吸管
Uh, he says the straw,
they're using it to penetrate a hole
‎他们在尝试用吸管戳洞
in... A box?
‎在一个盒子上戳？
[speaking russian]
okay, sorry, sorry.
‎好的 抱歉
[murray] the straw represents the
key, which emits a great energy.
‎吸管代表了钥匙 会发出巨大的能量
[speaking russian]
they're using this energy...
‎他们用这种能量
To break through a barrier,
‎冲破一个障碍
to open...
‎打开一个门...
A doorway.
A doorway between worlds.
‎不同世界之间的门
[alexei speaking russian]
[murray] but it seems this
key was only half the equation.
‎但看起来这个钥匙只是等式的一半
[speaking russian]
location... Location was the other half.
‎地点是另一半
[speaking russian]
oh, what...
‎哦 什么...
[speaking russian]
in hawkins, this door
had been opened once.
‎在霍金斯 这个门曾经被打开过一次
[speaking russian]
it was still...
‎它还在...
Healing.
‎复原中
Jesus christ.
‎老天
So, this door is open now?
‎所以 这个门现在是打开的？
[speaking russian]
he says it is...
‎他说这个门...
Opening.
‎正在打开
- [Creature shrieking]
- [fluttering sound]
[gasps]
- where are you going?
- To call our children.
‎-你要去哪儿？
‎-给我们的孩子们打电话
[gasps]
[in russian] can we
watch looney tunes now?
‎我们现在能看《乐一通》了吗？
Nyet.
[big band music playing]
[panting]
[grumbling]
- can I help you with something?
- Whiskey.
‎-要帮忙吗？
‎-威士忌
- You have whiskey?
- No, but I do have vodka.
‎-你有威士忌吗？
‎-没有 但我有伏特加
[hopper sighs]
- [hopper inhales sharply]
- oh!
If there's a way to start this key,
‎既然有办法打开这个钥匙
‎肯定就有办法制止 对不对？
there's gotta be a way to stop it, yeah?
Turn it off?
‎关掉？
- [Hopper inhales sharply]
- [murray sighs]
- right.
- Right?
‎-好了
‎-好了？
[in russian] the key, is
there a way to turn it off?
‎那把钥匙 有办法关掉吗？
[speaking russian]
[in english] he says, "of course
he could turn it off. Could...
‎他说 当然可以关掉
Edison not turn off a lamp,
could bell not hang up a phone?"
‎爱迪生没办法关灯吗？
‎贝尔没办法挂电话吗？
cocky bastard. "but..."
‎趾高气昂的混蛋 但是...
But what?
‎但是什么？
[speaking russian]
but he is now...
‎但他现在已经是"裸体"的了
"naked".
Sorry, "exposed". Compromised.
‎抱歉 暴露了 名誉扫地了
Hey, I will get you there.
‎嘿 我会送你过去
I will get you to your key.
‎我会把你送到你的钥匙身边
[speaking russian]
[laughs]
you wanna ask him what the
hell's so funny about that?
‎你想问问他有什么好笑的吗？
[speaking russian]
he says he likes your courage.
‎他说他很欣赏你的勇气
‎他觉得你像是个...
You remind him of a...
[clears throat]
... Fat rambo.
‎肥胖版的兰博
[alexei speaking russian]
[murray] but he says that even
thin rambo couldn't get there.
‎但他说 就连好身材的兰博都进不去
[alexei speaking russian]
this key, it is in an
underground fortress
‎这个钥匙在一个地下堡垒之中
designed by the greatest russian minds,
‎由最聪明的俄国人设计
guarded by their greatest warriors.
‎由最勇猛的战士们把守着
[speaking russian]
[murray] breaking in is...
‎想要闯进去是...
Impossible.
‎不可能的
Jackpot.
‎中头奖了
[dustin] oh-ho-ho!
Do you even know how to drive?
‎所以你会不会开车？
How hard can it be? Max did it.
‎能有多难？麦克斯都会开
- [Dustin] aw, come on.
- You seriously thought
‎-拜托
‎-你真的以为
- they'd just leave keys in there?
- There's gotta be a spare.
‎-他们会把钥匙插留那儿？
‎-肯定会有备用钥匙
[erica sighs]
- [erica] hey, dustin?
- Yeah?
‎-嘿 达斯汀？
‎-是？
How big did you say that demogorgon was?
‎你说那个魔王有多大来着？
Big. Nine feet or so. Why?
‎很大 两米七左右吧 怎么了？
Found 'em.
‎找到了
Erica?
‎艾瑞卡？
[loud zapping]
what the hell is that?!
‎这是什么鬼？
A deadly weapon.
‎致命武器 可能会派上用场
Could be useful.
- For what?
- What do you think?
‎-派什么用场？
‎-你以为呢？
Taking down commies,
saving your friends.
‎拿下共产党员 救你的朋友们
Thought you were more
realistic than that, nerd.
‎我还以为你比较务实呢 书呆子
We don't even know where they are,
‎我们都不知道它们在哪儿
and even if we did, there
are a million guards up there
‎就算知道 上面还有一百万个守卫
with weapons way deadlier than that.
‎他们的武器要比那玩意儿致命多了
The best thing we can do for them
‎我们要想帮他们
‎最好的选择就是跑出去找人帮忙
is to get out of here and find help.
Easy with that.
‎留神点
Our chance of surviving, and
theirs, rises substantially.
‎这样我们和他们的生存几率
‎都会大幅上升
Just trust me on this. Please?
‎就信我这一次吧 拜托？
[engine powering up]
[robin] help!
‎救命！
[robin's voice echoes]
help!
‎救命！
- Help!
- Hey, would you stop yelling?
‎-救命！
‎-嘿 你能别喊了吗？
Steve! Oh, my god!
‎史蒂夫 老天
[panting] steve...
‎史蒂夫
Are... Are you okay?
‎你没事吧？
My ears are ringing, and
I can't really breathe,
‎我的耳朵不停地响 喘不上气
my eye feels like it's
about to pop out of my skull,
‎眼睛像是要从眼眶里蹦出来一样
but, you know, apart from
that, I'm doing pretty good.
‎不过 除此之外 我挺好的
Well, the good news is that
they're calling you a doctor.
‎好消息是他们要给你找医生了
[robin chuckles]
is this his place of work?
‎这是他上班的地方吗？
- I love the vibe.
- [Robin chuckles]
‎这氛围不得不爱啊 真惹人爱
charming.
Yeah, tell me about it. So, okay,
‎是啊 可不是嘛
do you see that table
over there to your right?
‎你看到你右边那张桌子了吗？
‎不是 另一个右边
No, your other right.
- Oh.
- Yeah, okay.
‎-是的 好 看见剪刀了吗？
‎-没有
- And do you see those scissors?
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, well,
‎是 我觉得如果我们一起移动
‎就能移到那边
I think that if we move at the same
time, we could get over there,
and then maybe I could kick the
table and knock them into your lap.
‎然后也许我能踢一下桌子
‎把剪刀踢到你腿上
- And I could cut the binds.
- Yeah, and we could get out of here.
‎-然后我可以剪开绑带
‎-是的 然后我们就能逃走
- Gotcha. Okay, yeah, we can do that.
- Yeah.
‎-明白 是的 可以的
‎-是的
Those morons. They
left scissors in here?
‎那些蠢猪 居然留了剪刀在这里？
- Yeah, morons. [laughs]
- total morons.
‎-是啊 蠢猪
‎-绝对的蠢猪
- Okay.
- Okay, so,
‎-好的
‎-好的 所以
on the count of three, we're gonna hop.
‎我数到三 我们一起跳
- Okay, good, hop on three. I gotcha.
- All right.
‎-好的 数到三的时候跳 明白
‎-好的
One, two, three.
‎一 二 三
- Okay, that worked.
- Okay.
‎-好的 成功了
‎-好的
- All right. Uh, let's try again.
- Right.
‎好的 我们再试一次
[both] one, two, three.
‎一 二 三
- Holy shit, this is gonna work!
- We're close. Ready?
‎-老天 能成功的
‎-我们很接近了 准备好
Okay, one, two, three.
‎好了 一 二 三
[both grunting]
[both groaning]
[laughing lightly]
it's okay, it's okay.
‎没事的
Don't cry. Robin.
‎别哭 罗宾
[robin giggles]
are you laughing?
‎你是在笑吗？
[continues laughing]
- yeah.
- Jesus!
‎-是的
‎-老天
I'm sorry!
‎对不起
I'm so sorry. It's just...
‎真的很抱歉 只是...
I can't believe...
‎我不敢相信
I'm gonna die in a secret russian base
‎我要和史蒂夫"多毛"哈林顿一起
‎死在秘密俄国基地里了
with steve "the hair" harrington.
- It's just too trippy, man.
- We're not gonna die.
‎-太迷幻了 朋友
‎-我们不会死的
We're gonna get out of here, okay?
‎我们会逃出去的 好吗？
‎你给我点时间让我想一想
Just... You gotta let me
just think for a second.
Do you remember, um, mrs.
Click's sophomore history class?
‎你还记得克里克老师高二历史课吗？
What?
‎什么？
Mrs. Clickity-clackity.
‎噼噼啪啪老师
That's what us band dweebs called her.
‎我们乐队的呆子们都这么称呼她
- [Sighs]
- it was first period,
‎是第一节课
tuesdays and thursdays,
so you were always late.
‎每周二和周四的第一节课
‎所以你总是迟到
And you always had the same breakfast.
‎你总是吃一样的早饭
Bacon, egg, and cheese
on a sesame bagel.
‎芝麻贝果面包夹培根鸡蛋芝士
I sat behind you
‎我就坐在你后面
two days a week for a year.
‎那一整年每周有两天坐在你后面
Mister funny.
‎幽默先生
Mister cool.
‎酷炫先生
The king of hawkins high himself.
‎霍金斯高中之王本人
Do you even remember me from that class?
‎你还记得我上过那节课吗？
[robin chuckles]
of course you don't.
‎你当然不记得了
You were a real asshole, you know that?
‎你当时是个十足的大混蛋
‎你知道吗？
Yeah, I know.
‎是 我知道
But it didn't even matter.
‎但根本不重要
It didn't matter that you were an ass.
‎你是个大混蛋这一点丝毫不重要
I was still...
‎我那时仍然迷恋着你
Obsessed with you.
Even though all of us losers
pretend to be above it all,
‎虽然我们这些失败者们
‎假装超越了这一切
we still just wanna be popular...
‎我们仍旧想要受欢迎
Accepted,
‎被接受 做正常人
normal.
If it makes you feel any better,
‎如果能让你感觉好受一点的话
‎拥有这些并不是那么美好的事
having those things
isn't all that great.
Seriously.
‎我是认真的
[sighs] it just baffles me.
‎我只是非常困惑
Everything that people
tell you is important,
‎因为人们告诉你的每一件很重要的事
everything that people say you
should care about, it's all just...
‎人们说你需要关注的每一件事 都是...
[chuckles]
... Bullshit.
‎胡扯
But I guess you gotta mess up
to figure things out, right?
‎但我猜你得先搞砸了
‎才能搞明白这些 对吧？
I hope so.
‎希望如此
I feel like my whole life has been...
‎我觉得我这一辈子至今为止都是...
One big error.
‎一个巨大的错误
[chuckles]
yep. [laughs]
‎是的
at least it can't get any
more messed up than this.
‎至少不可能比现在更糟糕了
[both chuckle]
you know, I wish I'd
known you in click's class.
‎你知道吗
‎我希望在克里克的课上我就认识你
- Yeah?
- Really, I do.
‎-是吗？
‎-是的 真的
[robin chuckles]
maybe you could've
helped me pass the class.
‎也许你能帮我考过这门课
Maybe instead of being here, I'd
be on my way to college right now.
‎也许我现在就不会在这里
‎而是在去上大学的路上了
And I would have no idea
‎而我会完全不知道
that there were evil
russians beneath our feet,
‎还有邪恶的俄国人在我们的地下
and I would be happily slinging
ice cream with some other schmuck.
‎我会开心地
‎和另一个笨蛋一起卖冰淇淋
[both chuckle]
gotta say, though,
‎但我必须得说 我喜欢做你的笨蛋
I liked being your schmuck.
It was fun while it lasted.
‎做的时候还挺开心的
It was.
‎的确是
- [Buzzer sounds]
- [door opens]
[suspenseful music playing]
[chuckles]
where were you two going?
‎你们俩这是想去哪儿？
[clicking tongue]
try telling the truth this time, yes?
‎这次试着说实话吧 好吗？
It will make your visit with
dr. Zharkov less painful.
‎这样你看扎科夫医生的时候
‎就不会那么痛苦了
[winces]
[chuckles]
wait a second. Wait. Hold on.
‎等一下 慢着
Okay! Wait, wait, wait!
What is that thing?
‎好的 慢着！那是什么东西？
It will help you talk.
‎这会帮你坦白交代
Did you even clean that thing?!
‎你擦过了吗？
[screams]
[static hissing]
[gasping breaths]
[eleven breathes rapidly]
[gasping, panting]
what's he doing now?
‎他现在在干什么？
[nancy] and that's not normal, right?
‎这不正常 对吧？
Billy staying in his room
on the fourth of july?
‎独立日比利就待在自己房间里？
No, that's not normal.
‎没错 这不正常
He wants us to find him.
‎他想要我们找到他
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
‎是的 这正是我害怕的东西
If we go to billy, then
‎如果我们去找比利
‎剩下的被夺心的人就知道我们在哪儿
the rest of the flayed
know where we are.
It's a trap, I agree. We'll be ambushed.
‎这是个陷阱 我同意 我们会被伏击的
We won't be surprised.
‎我们不会被偷袭
We'll know that they're coming,
‎我们会知道他们要来 我们会把这些
‎被夺心的人打得屁滚尿流
and we will kick their flayed butts.
You mean el will kick their butts.
‎你指的是艾尔会把他们打得屁滚尿流
[eleven's voice echoes] papa!
‎爸爸！
no.
‎不
[terry] rainbow. Three to
the right, four to the left.
‎彩虹 三放在右边 四放在左边 彩虹
Sunflower. Rainbow.
- [Mike] it's too risky.
- [Nancy] yeah, and unnecessary.
‎-太冒险了
‎-是的 而且没必要
Killing the flayed won't
stop the mind flayer.
‎杀掉被夺心者不会阻止夺心魔
We have to find out
where it's spreading from.
‎我们必须找到是从哪儿传播出来的
We have to find the source.
‎我们必须找到源头
[eleven] billy knows it.
‎比利知道在哪里
Billy's been there.
‎比利去过那里
To the source.
‎源头
- Yeah, but...
- It's a trap. I know.
‎-是的 但是...
‎-这是个陷阱 我知道
[eleven] we can't go to billy,
‎我们不能去找比利
but I think there's another way.
‎但我觉得有另一种办法
A way for me to see where he's been.
‎能让我能看到他去过什么地方
[static hissing]
el, I know you think you have
to do this, but you don't.
‎艾尔 我知道你觉得你必须这么做
‎但不是这样的
It's just, you've only
done this before once.
‎你之前只这么做过一次
And your mom, she loved you,
‎而且你妈妈她深爱着你
and wanted you to know what happened.
‎想要你知道发生了什么
And billy's mind is...
Is sick, diseased.
‎比利的脑子生病了
The mind flayer is in him.
‎夺心魔在他身体内
He can't hurt me.
‎他无法伤害到我的
Not in there.
‎在那里面伤害不了
We don't know that.
‎这我们不知道的
Mike.
‎迈克
I need you to trust me.
‎我需要你信任我
Yeah.
‎好吧 自己小心
Just... Be careful.
[shivering breaths]
[eleven exhales sharply]
[echoing] billy.
‎比利
Can you hear me?
‎能听到我说话吗？
I want to see.
‎我想看看
I want to see what happened.
‎我想看看发生了什么
[suspenseful synth music playing]
[whimpering]
something's wrong.
‎不对劲了
[screams] stop! No! No! No!
‎停下！不！
no!
[distorted roaring]
[gasping]
[billy grunting]
[tires screeching]
[distorted screams]
[squawking]
[distorted wailing]
[mike, echoing] el, are you okay?
‎艾尔 你没事吧？
Are you okay?
‎你没事吧？
[sighs]
[softly] I'm okay.
‎我没事
What's going on?
‎出什么事了？
I'm... On a beach.
‎我在一个海滩上
[lucas] okay, I may be dense,
‎好吧 我知道我比较笨
but the last I checked,
‎但据我所知
there weren't any beaches in hawkins.
‎霍金斯没有海滩
What else do you see?
‎你还看到了什么？
[tides crashing]
[seagulls squawking]
[eleven] a woman.
‎一个女人
She's...
‎她...
Pretty.
‎很漂亮
i...
‎我...
I think she's looking at me.
‎我觉得她在看着我
[echoing laughter]
[woman] woo!
Yeah!
‎耶！
[woman laughs]
[woman] you did it!
‎你做到了！
There's...
‎有一个...小男孩
A boy.
Did you see that?
‎你看到了吗？
Yeah, I saw that!
‎是的 我看到了
That was at least seven feet.
‎至少有两米长
[woman] I don't know what it was,
‎我不知道那是什么
‎但我差点吓得心脏病都发了
but it almost gave me a heart attack.
Ten more minutes?
‎再玩十分钟？
- Yeah, okay, ten more minutes.
- Okay.
‎好的 再玩十分钟
But any longer than that,
dad's gonna be mad, okay?
‎超过十分钟爸爸就要生气了 好吗？
[boy] okay!
‎好的
[boy panting]
billy?
‎比利？
Watch out for rip currents!
‎小心离岸流
I know.
‎我知道
It's billy.
‎是比利
It's california.
‎在加州
It's a memory.
‎是一段记忆
[seagulls squawking]
[distant rumbling]
I think I see it.
‎我觉得我看到了
The source.
‎源头
[panting]
[ominous synth music playing]
[thunder rumbling and crashing]
[dialing on rotary phone]
[murray] two minutes, jim.
‎两分钟 吉姆
It's a secure line,
‎这个是安全线路
‎但超过两分钟 他们就能追踪你
but any longer than that
and they could trace you.
Yeah, I want 'em to trace me.
‎-对 我想要他们追踪我
‎-什么？
- What?
- [Hopper clears throat]
[phone ringing]
philadelphia public library.
‎费城公共图书馆
Uh...
This is jim hopper...
‎我是吉姆·霍珀
Uh... Police chief, hawkins.
‎霍金斯的警察局长
[hopper] I got this
number from Dr. Sam owens.
‎山姆欧文斯博士给我的这个号码
What is your identification code?
‎你的身份暗号是什么？
Identification code?
‎身份暗号？
You don't know it?
‎你不知道？
You must be joking.
‎你开玩笑吧
Oh, no, no, I got it, I got it.
‎不 我有的
[chuckles] I got it.
You wrote it down and
kept it in your wallet?
‎你写在了纸上 然后放在了皮夹里？
"antique chariot". Listen.
‎古董战车 听着
[hopper] um, tell owens that the
russkies are opening the gate.
‎告诉欧文斯俄国人在打开大门
Now, he'll know what that means.
‎他会明白的 不是俄国人
‎他会明白大门的部分
Not about the russkies,
but about the gate.
Tell him that there's an
entrance at starcourt mall.
‎告诉他星庭商场有个入口
I know how to get in,
‎我知道怎么进去
but I need backup, a lot of backup.
‎但我需要支援 很多后援
Have him call me back
here at 618-625-8313.
‎叫他给我回电话
‎号码是6186258313
Your message will be relayed.
‎我们会转达你的消息的
- So, now what?
- Now, we, uh...
‎-现在怎么办？
‎-现在我们...
We wait.
‎等着
You compromised me, jim.
‎你把我给暴露了 吉姆
You do realize that, don't
you? I'm gonna have to relocate.
‎你意识到了吧？我这下得搬家了
- How long do we wait?
- As long as it takes.
‎-等多久？
‎-需要多久就等多久
How can you just sit there being calm?
‎你怎么能就那么冷静地坐在那里？
I am not calm!
‎我一点都不冷静
Our kids are in danger!
‎我们的孩子们有危险
You said they were at the festival!
‎你说他们去了嘉年华
Which is, like, ten
minutes from the gate!
‎那地方离门只有十分钟车程
[scoffs]
what are you doing? Joyce?
‎你干什么 乔伊斯？
What are you doing?
‎你干什么？
[phone rings]
philadelphia public library.
‎费城公共图书馆
Yes, hello.
‎是的 你好 我是古董战车的搭档
Uh, this is, uh, antique
chariot's partner...
Wheelbarrow.
‎手推车
I don't think antique chariot
‎我觉得古董战车并没有
properly conveyed the
urgency of our situation.
‎完全表达出我们目前处境的紧急程度
What are you doing?
‎-你在干什么？
‎-我们不能干坐着
Can't just sit around
and wait for a call.
‎等电话
- Ma'am, I'm gonna need you to stay calm.
- No.
‎-女士 我需要你保持冷静
‎-不
Don't you dare patronize me!
‎你可别高人一等
I don't know who you are,
‎我不知道你是谁
if you're some glorified
secretary or what,
‎是个美化了的秘书还是什么的
but if you don't wanna lose your job,
‎但是如果你不想丢饭碗
‎就照我说的做
here's what's gonna happen.
When I hang up,
‎等我挂了电话
you're gonna get up off your ass,
‎你就把屁股从椅子上挪开
and you're gonna go find owens
and tell him what's going on.
‎去找到欧文斯 告诉他发生了什么
We don't have time to talk
about it and neither does he.
‎我们没时间讨论了 他也没时间了
He's gotta get to hawkins,
‎他必须要马上来霍金斯
‎现在就把他的后援给带来！
and he's gotta bring his men right now!
Do you understand me?
‎你明白我说的话吗？
Yes, yes, ma'am.
‎是的 女士
Thank you. And good day.
‎谢谢你 祝你今天愉快
It's been exactly one minute, joyce.
‎才过了整整一分钟而已 乔伊斯
That's one minute too long.
‎那也是多等了一分钟
- Alexei.
- [Gasps]
‎阿列克谢
[in russian] what's going on?
‎怎么了？
We gotta go. Vroom, vroom.
‎我们得走了
Back to hawkins. Come on.
‎回霍金斯 快来吧
[joyce] come on.
‎来吧
Honestly, I don't really feel anything.
‎老实说 我都感觉不到任何东西
Do you?
‎你呢？
I mean, I... I feel fine.
‎我想说 我感觉挺好
- I feel normal.
- Yeah, I feel... I feel fine.
‎-感觉挺正常的
‎-是的 我也觉得不错
I kinda feel good.
‎还觉得挺好的
[both chuckling]
- wanna know a secret?
- What?
‎-想知道一个秘密吗？
‎-什么？
I like it, too!
‎我也喜欢这种感觉
[both laugh]
- I feel good.
- Morons. They messed up the drug.
‎-我觉得很好
‎-蠢蛋 他们把药给搞砸了
They messed it up!
‎他们搞砸了
- Morons. Hey, morons!
- Morons!
‎-蠢蛋 嘿 蠢蛋！
‎-蠢蛋！
- Moron! Mor...
- Hey!
‎-蠢蛋！
‎-嘿！
Whoa-oh!
Oh, no. There's definitely
something wrong with us.
‎哦 不 我们绝对有什么地方不对劲了
- Something's wrong.
- [Door buzzer sounds]
‎有些不对劲
[robin chuckles]
would now be a good time to tell
you that I don't like doctors?
‎现在告诉你我不喜欢医生
‎是不是时机不太恰当？
Let's try this again, yes?
‎我们再试一遍吧 好吗？
[murmurs]
who do you work for?
‎你为谁工作？
Scoops. [chuckles]
‎冰淇淋店 水手冰淇淋
scoops ahoy.
[giggles]
how did you find us?
‎你是怎么找到我们的？
Totally by accident. [chuckles]
‎绝对是意外
[steve chuckles]
[in russian] more lies.
‎更多的谎言
What is that shiny little toy?
‎-那个亮闪闪的玩具是什么？
‎-你要用那玩意儿干什么？
[robin] where you going with that, doc?
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
Wait! No! Wait! Wait!
‎哦 哇 嘿 等一下！
- Whoa!
- There was a code! We heard a code!
‎有个代码 我们听到了一个代码
Code.
‎代码
What code?
‎什么代码？
"the week is long.
‎一周漫长
The silver cat feeds when
blue meets yellow in the west."
‎银色的猫会在西方蓝黄相交时进食
Blah, blah, blah.
You broadcast that stupid
spy shit all over town,
‎你们把你们愚蠢的破间谍玩意儿
‎全城广播
and we picked it up on our cerebro,
‎我们的脑波强化仪接收到了
and we cracked it in a day.
‎一天就破解了
A day!
‎一天
You think you're so smart,
‎你们以为自己很聪明
but a couple of kids who
scoop ice cream for a living
‎但几个以卖冰淇淋为生的孩子
cracked your code in a day, and
now, people know you're here.
‎一天就破解了你们的代码
‎现在 人们知道你们在这里了
Who knows we are here, little bitch?
‎谁知道我们在这里了 婊子？
Uh, well, dustin knows.
‎达斯汀就知道
Hey, steve?
‎嘿 史蒂夫？
- Yeah, dustin henderson, he knows.
- Steve!
‎-是 达斯汀亨德森 他就知道
‎-史蒂夫！
- [Steve laughs]
- dustin henderson.
‎达斯汀亨德森
It is your small, curly-haired friend?
‎是你那个卷发的小个子朋友吗？
Oh, curly-haired. Great hair.
Small. Kind of like a 'fro. Yeah.
‎卷发 是的 头发可好了 小个子
‎有点像爆炸头 是的
Where is he?
‎他在哪儿？
He's long gone, you big asshole.
‎他早就跑了 你个大混蛋
And he's probably calling hopper,
‎他八成在打电话给霍珀
and hopper's calling
the us cavalry. [laughs]
‎霍珀在给美国政府打电话
they're gonna come in here,
commando-style, guns a-blazin',
‎他们会冲进来
‎突击队模式全开 荷枪实弹
and kick your sorry
asses back to russia.
‎把你们都给一脚踹回俄国去
You're gonna be two pieces of toast.
‎你们俩会变成两块烤面包
[snickers]
is that so?
‎是吗？
Yeah.
‎是啊
[both laugh]
[laughs]
‎是的
[alarm blaring]
[soldiers yelling in russian]
[speaking russian]
[officer grunts a command]
- [sizzling]
- [electricity crackling]
[intense synth music playing]
[yells]
[screaming]
hey! Henderson!
‎嘿 亨德森！
That's crazy, I was
just talking about you.
‎好疯狂 我刚刚还说起你
- Oh, my god!
- Get ready to run.
‎-哦 老天
‎-准备好逃跑
[thunder rumbling]
[wind howling]
[ominous synth music playing]
[man] hey! Billy, stop!
‎嘿 比利 停下！
What the hell is wrong with
you? What did we talk about, huh?
‎你究竟什么毛病？我们怎么说的？
You gotta slide!
‎你必须要滑进二垒
- [Stammering] I know.
- Wait.
‎-我知道
‎-什么？
- Afraid you're gonna get hurt, is that it?
- No.
‎-你怕自己会受伤 是不是？
‎-不是的
[man] well, what then? What?
‎那是为什么？
What did I raise, a pussy for a son?
‎我养了个什么？没种的儿子？
- Leave me alone!
- Hey!
‎-别纠缠我了！
‎-嘿！
[man] that's right,
run! Like you always do!
‎是啊 逃跑吧 你就会逃跑
[lightning crackling]
[thunderclap]
[man] where were you last
night? Where were you?
‎你昨晚去哪儿了？
- [Woman] I told you, I was with wendy.
- [Man] stop lying to me!
‎-我告诉你了 我和温蒂在一起
‎-别撒谎了
- [Woman] I'm not lying to you!
- You saw him again, didn't you?
‎-我没有撒谎
‎-你又去见他了 是不是？
- Didn't you?!
- Get away from me!
‎-是不是？
‎-放开我！
- I said, get away!
- You... You whore!
‎-我叫你放开我！
‎-你个荡妇！
- Stop it!
- Bitch!
‎-住手！
‎-婊子！
- Don't hurt her!
- No!
‎-别伤害她！
‎-不！
- Don't hurt her!
- [Woman] you bastard!
‎-别伤害她！
‎-混账！
[man grunts]
[young billy] mom!
‎妈妈！
[young billy] I don't
understand. Why not?
‎我不明白 为什么不行？
Please, mom, don't do this.
‎拜托了 妈妈 别这样
Please come home.
‎求你回家吧
No. How long? How long?!
‎不 要多久？
[sobbing] I Miss you.
‎我想你了
[teen billy] get back here!
‎快回来！
[grunting]
get up! What, are you
scared to fight me?
‎站起来！怎么？你害怕和我打吗？
You scared?
‎害怕了？
Get up and fight me, pussy! Pussy!
‎站起来和我打啊 没种的
[man] billy, come over here,
I want you to meet someone.
‎比利 你过来 我想要你见个人
This is your new sister.
Her name's maxine.
‎这是你的新妹妹 她叫麦克辛
max.
‎麦克斯
- Shake her hand.
- [Billy] who's there?
‎-握她的手
‎-是谁？
[man] I said, shake her hand.
‎-我叫你握她的手
‎-我问了 是谁？
[billy] I said, who's there?! [screams]
[billy screams]
[screaming continues]
[lightning crackling]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder rumbling and booming]
I think I found it.
‎我觉得我找到了
[eleven panting]
the source.
‎源头
Where, el? Where are you?
‎在哪里 艾尔？你在哪里？
Brimborn...
‎布里波恩炼钢厂
Steelworks.
Here. Okay, uh,
steelworks, steelworks...
‎好的 在这儿 炼钢厂
Uh...
Here, steel.
‎找到了 炼钢厂...
Uh...
[jonathan] found it.
6522 cherry oak drive.
‎找到了 樱桃橡木路6522号
- That's close.
- El, el, we found it. Get out of there.
‎-离这里很近
‎-艾尔 我们找到了 快出来
[mike] get out.
‎快出来
[echoing scream]
[distorted scream]
[gasps]
[panting]
mike?
‎迈克？
Mike?
[whimpers]
mike!
‎迈克！
[echoing] mike!
[billy, with deep
voice] he can't hear you.
‎他听不见你说话
[gasps]
you shouldn't have looked for me.
‎你不应该来找我的
Because now I see you.
‎因为现在 我看到你了
Now we can all see you.
‎现在 我们都能看到你了
[dramatic choral music playing]
[cheering and laughing]
you...
‎你...
Let us in.
‎把我们放了进来
[creature roaring]
and now...
‎现在
You are going to have to let us stay.
‎你必须要让我们留下来
[boy laughing]
david, where you going?
‎大卫 你去哪儿？大卫？
David?
[excited cheering]
adam!
‎亚当！
You're gonna Miss it!
‎你要错过了
Adam!
‎亚当！
[firecrackers crackling]
don't you see?
‎没发现吗？
All this time,
‎这么长时间以来
we've been building it.
‎我们一直在积累...
- [Sobbing]
- we've been building it...
‎我们一直在积累着...
For you.
‎是为你积累的
All that work,
‎那么多的工作
all that pain...
‎那么多的痛苦
All of it... For you.
‎所有这些...都是为了你
- [Eleven sobbing]
- and now it's time.
‎而现在 时候到了
Time to end it.
‎结束的时候到了
And we are going to end you.
‎我们会把你干掉
And when you are gone,
‎等你不在了
we are going to end your friends.
‎-我们会干掉你的朋友们
‎-不！
- No!
- And then we are going to end...
‎然后 我们会干掉...
Everyone.
‎所有人
[screaming] get away!
‎滚开！
no!
‎不！
El, you're okay. It's... It's okay.
‎你没事吧？艾尔 怎么了？
el.
‎艾尔！
[sobbing]
[low frequency rumbling]
[creature shrieking]
[choking noises]
[creature snarls]
[creature lowing]
[choking noises]
[squelching noises]
[creature shrieking]
[creature snarls]
[man grunts]
[squelching noises]
[pounding and rattling gate]
[creature shrieks]
[roaring]
[dramatic orchestral and
choral music continues]
‎字幕制作：美国青少年英语 （微信公众号&喜马拉雅主播）
[monkey screeches]